{
    "subject": "resource/Sani_Emmanuel",
    "predicate": "property/clubs",
    "object": "resource/Oskarshamns_AIK",
    "human_readable": "Sani Emmanuel plays for Oskarshamns AIK.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9151487946510315,
            "question": "Who plays for Oskarshamns AIK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8313941359519958,
            "question": "What is the name of the athlete who plays for Oskarshamns AIK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8129110336303711,
            "question": "What team does Sani Emmanuel play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7720575332641602,
            "question": "What is the name of the team Sani Emmanuel plays for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658769249916077,
            "question": "Where does Sani Emmanuel play his games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5913782715797424,
            "question": "Is Sani Emmanuel a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5297701358795166,
            "question": "What level of competition does Oskarshamns AIK play at?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5191146731376648,
            "question": "Is Oskarshamns AIK a popular team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4485245645046234,
            "question": "In what sport does Sani Emmanuel compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25327229499816895,
            "question": "Has Sani Emmanuel won any awards for his performance?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sani Emmanuel plays for Oskarshamns AIK.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3333_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what sport does Sani Emmanuel compete?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3333_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Oskarshamns AIK a popular team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3333_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What level of competition does Oskarshamns AIK play at?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3333_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3333_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* In file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3333/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt, it is mentioned that \"The 22-year-old Emmanuel played for Swedish lower league team Oskarshamns AIK in 2015 where he played four games and scored a goal.\"\n* In file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3333/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt, it is mentioned that \"23 year old Sani last season played just 50 minutes of top flight football appearing four times as a substitute for Swedish side Oskarshamns AIK.\"\n\nThis information supports the triple that Sani Emmanuel plays for Oskarshamns AIK.\n\nTherefore, the response in JSON format is:\n\n```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"23 year old Sani last season played just 50 minutes of top flight football appearing four times as a substitute for Swedish side Oskarshamns AIK.\" This supports the triple that Sani Emmanuel plays for Oskarshamns AIK."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}